The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Death aura ?
The flame metal is a yang-attribute ore.
So why is the death aura
so dense on Planet Yun Xia ?
Planet Yun Xia is not in some remote place.
How can there not be a single human on this planet ?
That is...
Moongazer Serpent\NNirvana Scryer
A Moongazer Serpent !?
How could this thing exist here ?
I saw in Tu Si's memory,
that Moongazer Serpents are parasites living in Ancient God's bodies.
They survive by feeding on Ancient God Blood.
The Moongazer Serpents don't harm the Ancient God's massive body
and can even be used by the Ancient God like artifacts.
Once an Ancient God dies,
the Moongazer Serpents die alongside it.
It's almost impossible for them to survive.
Back then, Tu Si had been dead for so long
that there was no trace of Moongazer Serpents
in the Land of the Ancient God.
Could it be that Planet Yun Xia
has the remains of another Ancient God ?
If that's really the case,
how could the leaders of the Allheaven Star System
be ignoring it like that ?
This place is strange.
I need to quickly find that flame metal vein.
1 hour later
There really is a flame metal vein here !
Flame metal vein\NPlanet Yun Xia
This...
This entire ore vein is ours !
Master,
we've struck it rich !
What are you waiting for ?
Just give me the order
and Little Xu will start digging it right away !
Something's wrong...
This flame metal vein
isn't buried deep enough.
Any Ascendant cultivator
could find it easily.
Such a precious treasure
cannot possibly survive the countless millennia.
Moreover,
if it were a naturally formed ore,
it should not be so pure and regular.
This thing
looks more like a bone.
These aren't trees...
They're tentacles !
The whole Planet Yun Xia
is the skeleton made of flame metal
of a giant sleeping Moongazer Serpent !
If I had tried to excavate the flame metal vein earlier,
it would have likely awakened the Moongazer Serpent.
And I wouldn't have survived
against this giant beast.
Throughout history,
those who coveted the flame metal vein
have likely all died here.
But this flame metal vein is crucial for the Heaven Defying Bead...
I am determined to obtain it !
I will need to find another way
to extract it.
Illusion Moon Pool\NPlanet Thousand Illusions
Huan Mei,
after the blood exchange ritual
you
will truly become a member of the Huan Family.
No matter what you do,
don't betray the blood of the Huan Family !
Ten thousand illusions as the soul,
Ten thousand drops of blood as the guide,
I Huan Wuqing, a member of the 26th generation of the Huan Family,
humbly requests
the ancestral bloodline !
A long time ago,
my Huan Family's ancestor was a Celestial of the Thunder Celestial Realm.
Although the Celestial Realm was destroyed,
the bloodline still remains.
This blood exchange ritual
refines the purest bloodline
from the blood of tens of thousands of disciples
to create a blood imprint on a person's body.
Today, even the Ancestor
has willingly lowered his own cultivation by one realm
by personally infusing a large amount of his essence blood into this imprint
to cleanse her meridians.
Why is he paying such a price
just for her sake !?
Ten thousand illusions
Identityless !
The Ancestor's Ten Thousand Illusions Identityless Dao
Ten Thousand Illusions\NIdentityless Dao
is the pinnacle of the Huan Family
but doesn't have a successor.
Could it be that the Ancestor's gesture of imparting his teachings
is to nurture a successor who follows his Dao ?
Huan Mei\NPeak Late stage\NAscendant
Something's wrong !
How is that possible ?
Her domain
is evolving !
The domains left behind by the family's Ancient Celestials
were the Heavenly Devil and Identityless Daos.
The strongest was the Heavenly Devil Dao
but was long lost.
Yet the aura of this woman's domain...
Could it be...
A domain evolution
is unheard of !
Was this
the Ancestor's plan ?
Thousand Illusions\NHeavenly Devil Dao
Mei'er
thanks the Ancestor for giving me a new life.
Huan Wuqing\NCorporeal Yang\N(originally Nirvana Scryer)
You truly
didn't disappoint me !
Ancestors of the Huan Family,
do you see this !?
The Ten Thousand Illusions Heavenly Devil Dao that was long lost by the Huan Family,
sees the light of day once more !
Huan Mei,
this is your first battle as a member of the Huan Family.
Go to Planet Ran Yun
and carve out your fearsome reputation !
Planet Sealing Formation\NPlanet Ran Yun
Don't waste your energy.
Even with the three of us,
this Planet Sealing Formation
cannot be broken.
Then what should we do ?
If we don't break the formation,
then are we waiting to die !?
This matter
is likely meant to establish Huan Mei's reputation.
Fellow cultivator Xu Mu said
he would return
in 3 months.
The Huan Family isn't even here yet
and this person has already fled !
Why would he come back !?
She's here !
Are the Ancestors of the families of Ran Yun
you three ?
Is she really...
Huan Mei ?
Will our Planet Ran Yun
really be exterminated by a frail woman
all alone ?
Brother Sun, Brother Zhao,
a great calamity is upon us today.
Let's fight without any restraint !
Even if we die,
we won't have any regrets !
Brother Ran is so heroic !
Since you are burning your Origin Soul,
then I
will accompany you !
Forget it !
How could I
fall behind you guys !?
That's very thoughtful of you three.
Since you're all willingly fighting to the death,
it saves me a lot of trouble.
Dao comprehension !?
You...
If you're going to burn your Origin Souls,
burn them more thoroughly.
Brother Zhao,
wake up !
Brother Sun,
help me !
What kind of
Dao comprehension is this ?
You could have also confused my mind
but you purposely kept me awake
to be slaughtered by my allies !
What a vicious tactic...
Have I
ever raised a hand on you ?
You three just fought among yourselves.
It doesn't have anything to do with me.
With the Ten Thousand Illusions Heavenly Devil Dao,
I never need allies to fight with me.
Wherever I go,
countless cultivators will fight for me
and die for me.
Given your strength,
you three can't be the ones who killed Huan Dong.
Who else
was there ?
You three sacrificed your bodies
and ignited your Origin Souls as a diversion.
Did you think I wouldn't see through it ?
You still have avatars to save yourselves.
Please spare my life,
that person is named is Xu Mu !
He's the one
who killed the member of your Huan Family.
He left this place 2 days ago.
If you want to find his trail,
I...
I can help you !
No rush.
One by one.
Once stained with the blood of the Huan Family,
no one can escape.
When I left a few days ago,
there wasn't such a restriction on Planet Ran Yun.
This formation is quite complex.
Breaking it will take some time
But entering the formation
is easy.
Ice Plains\NPlanet Ran Yun
Sun Xi's avatar\NLate stage Core Formation
It's her !
Peak Late stage Ascendant ?
I am not confident
in fighting her.
But I have changed my appearance using the Celestial Guard's spells.
She shouldn't recognize me.
This avatar was for saving my life,
I have never told anyone its location.
How did she
find it so easily !?
You ignited your Origin Soul
yet succumbed to your own desires.
You fought to the death
while keeping an avatar to save yourself.
How much of your righteousness
is even genuine ?
That's really interesting.
Fellow cultivator Xu,
save me !
Fellow cultivator Sun,
you didn't tell me
that you have an avatar.
Well...
I suppose you were planning to have me fight to the death with the Huan Family
and whether I succeeded or not,
you could use this avatar to save yourself.
Am I wrong ?
Although you lack honor,
I have taken your celestial jades
so I will protect you this time.
I advise you not to meddle.
Now...
leave Planet Ran Yun.
I didn't expect
that your cultivation had also reached Ascendant.
Did you really think that by hiding your appearance
and changing your aura,
I wouldn't recognize you ?
Wang Lin !
But at Early stage Ascendant,
you are destined to die here !
Back then on Planet Suzaku
when you destroyed my domain,
I used the Thousand Illusions Ruthless Dao
to glimpse at your obsessions.
Today,
by destroying your Dao Heart
and shattering your obsessions,
I will fulfill my hatred !
Wang Lin,
I will send you
to reunite with Li Muwan !
You're seeking death !
What kind of spell is this ?
When I look with my Divine Sense,
this person looks exactly like the real Red Butterfly.
But it's just an illusion !
Stop playing tricks !
Uncle...
You...
Are you going to kill Little Ru'er ?
An illusion...
This is also an illusion.
Disciple,
remember to pass down the Billion Soul Flag
and make the Soul Refining Sect of Planet Suzaku
flourish again.
Wang Lin !
Junior Brother !
Illusions...
Son...
Senior...
come back.
The Ten Thousand Illusions Heavenly Devil Dao
can borrow the opponent's memories
to ignite their Origin Soul
and burn their body and soul.
All it takes is a moment of weakness
to be at my mercy.
Wang Lin,
your Origin Soul has been ignited.
The outcome
is already decided !
Thunder !?
How could there be thunder energy
in his Origin Soul !?
How is this possible !?
When karma has been resolved,
the heart doesn't have regrets
and can be at peace.
But if karma hasn't been resolved,
then even in the face of the will of the heavens,
it must be defied.
This is the Dao I understood
when I reached Ascendant.
My obsessions
cannot be controlled by your mere domain !
Although your cultivation was forcibly raised,
our domains
are worlds apart.
Your domain
cannot break this Dao Heart.
Your illusions
cannot ignite
my Origin Soul !
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.